.
.
Sir,
سيد،
don't come to the kitchen anymore.
لا تأتي إلى المطبخ بعد الآن.
Just leave these things to me.
فقط اترك هذه الأشياء لي.
Miss Su likes to be independent,
الآنسة سو تحب أن تكون مستقلة ،
and do her own thing.
وتفعل الشيء الخاص بها.
So I'm going to start by making breakfast.
لذلك سأبدأ بإعداد وجبة الإفطار.
Uncle Wang,
العم وانغ ،
I may have to ask you to hide for a while.
قد أطلب منك الاختباء لبعض الوقت.
When Bunny and I finish dinner and go to the college together,
عندما ننتهي أنا وباني من العشاء ونذهب إلى الكلية معًا ،
can you come out again?
هل يمكنك الخروج مرة أخرى؟
Sure,
بالتأكيد،
go ahead.
تفضل.
Little rabbit,
أرنب صغير
how does it taste?
كيف طعمها؟
It's pretty good.
إنه جيد جدًا.
What about the clue
ماذا عن الدليل
to the Heart of Stallone?
إلى قلب ستالون؟
I'm going to be angry.
سأغضب.
I'll put up with you till tonight,
سوف أتحمل معك حتى الليلة ،
of course,
بالطبع،
We have the key information.
لدينا المعلومات الأساسية.
There's nothing I, Ouyang Yuchuan, can't do.
لا يوجد شيء لا أستطيع فعله أنا أويانغ يوتشوان.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Don't you know breaking into a house is illegal?
الا تعلم ان اقتحام منزل غير قانوني؟
Mr. Ouyang,
السيد أويانغ ،
we're doing measurement work
نحن نقوم بعمل القياس
for the owner of this new house,
لصاحب هذا المنزل الجديد ،
Please cooperate with me.
الرجاء التعاون معي.
What?
ماذا؟
When did I invite you to do the measurement?
متى دعوتك لعمل القياس؟
Don't you know?
الا تعلم؟
The house has been sold.
تم بيع المنزل.
You are no longer the owner of this place.
لم تعد مالك هذا المكان.
Please move out immediately.
يرجى الخروج على الفور.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Get the hell out of here!
اخرج من هنا بحق الجحيم!
Old man, you're the ones who should get out of here, right?
أيها الرجل العجوز ، أنت من يجب أن تخرج من هنا ، أليس كذلك؟
Uncle Wang,
العم وانغ ،
don't argue with these workers yet,
لا تجادل مع هؤلاء العمال حتى الآن ،
When I get back,
عندما اعود،
I'll ask my father about it,
سوف أسأل والدي عن ذلك ،
You'd better ask your dad what's going on.
من الأفضل أن تسأل والدك عما يحدث.
Manager Wang,
مدير وانغ ،
you're here
أنت هنا
to help with the kitchen,
للمساعدة في المطبخ ،
-Yes. -Help the
-نعم.  -مساعدة
kitchen.
مطبخ.
It's quite delicious.
إنه لذيذ جدا.
Father,
أب،
a group of people came to the old house today
جاءت مجموعة من الناس إلى المنزل القديم اليوم
and said that our old house was sold,
وقلنا أن منزلنا القديم تم بيعه ،
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
Why?
لماذا؟
Is our family short of money?
هل عائلتنا تعاني من نقص في المال؟
The most important thing our family needs is money.
أهم شيء تحتاجه عائلتنا هو المال.
But the amount offered by the buyer
لكن المبلغ الذي عرضه المشتري
is really hard for me to refuse.
من الصعب حقًا بالنسبة لي أن أرفض.
Sir,
سيد،
Master,
يتقن،
This ancient mansion is a witness to Ouyang's family's business.
هذا القصر القديم شاهد على أعمال عائلة Ouyang.
It symbolizes the glory of the family. You
إنه يرمز إلى مجد الأسرة.  أنت
can't sell it.
لا يمكن بيعها.
I'm a businessman.
أنا رجل أعمال.
As long as I can make more money,
طالما يمكنني كسب المزيد من المال ،
is to give the family the greatest glory.
هو اعطاء العائلة المجد الاعظم.
In half an hour,
خلال نصف ساعة،
the buyer will check in.
سيقوم المشتري بتسجيل الوصول.
Take them to pack up.
خذهم لحزم أمتعتهم.
Tell that silly girl to move out right now!
أخبر تلك الفتاة السخيفة بالخروج الآن!
Yes
نعم
Su Shengnan, I'm talking to you.
سو شنغنان ، أنا أتحدث إليكم.
I'll give you one minute to move out of here.
سأعطيك دقيقة واحدة لتخرج من هنا.
You didn't help me clean it up and you asked me to move it?
لم تساعدني في تنظيفه وطلبت مني تحريكه؟
My goodness,
رباه،
Miss Leng,
ملكة جمال لينغ ،
What are you doing in my house?
ماذا تفعل في منزلي؟
Ouyang, what are you talking about?
اويانغ ، ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
This is our wedding room.
هذه غرفة زفافنا.
Have you lost your mind to me?
هل فقدت عقلك لي؟
Ouyang's brother and uncle haven't told you yet?
لم يخبرك شقيق أويانج وعمه بعد؟
What?
ماذا؟
My brother has bought this place.
لقد اشترى أخي هذا المكان.
This will be our wedding room from now on.
ستكون هذه غرفة زفافنا من الآن فصاعدًا.
Brother,
أخ،
How can you spend so much money
كيف يمكنك انفاق الكثير من المال
on an old mansion again?
في قصر قديم مرة أخرى؟
I bought it for you.
لقد اشتريتها لك.
I have enough houses.
لدي منازل كافية.
I don't want that old mansion, do I?
لا أريد هذا القصر القديم ، أليس كذلك؟
You must have been cheated.
لابد أنك تعرضت للغش.
Silly girl,
فتاة سخيفة،
that's the wedding room
هذه غرفة الزفاف
I bought for you,
اشتريت لك
Yes.
نعم.
That old mansion.
هذا القصر القديم.
Symbolizing the glory of Ouyang's family,
يرمز إلى مجد عائلة أويانغ ،
I bought it at a high price,
اشتريته بسعر مرتفع ،
Then I'll send it to Ouyang's family.
ثم سأرسله إلى عائلة أويانغ.
To prove my approval of this marriage.
لإثبات موافقتي على هذا الزواج.
So you've been caring about me.
إذا كنت تهتم بي.
Silly. So, as the hostess,
سخيف.  لذلك ، بصفتي المضيفة ،
you should move in.
يجب عليك الانتقال.
Am I right?
هل انا على حق؟
I'm not going.
أنا لن أذهب.
Because Su Shengnan is there,
لأن Su Shengnan موجودة ،
I don't want to see her.
لا اريد ان اراها.
That's why I'm not going.
لهذا السبب لن أذهب.
It's fine if you don't go.
لا بأس إذا لم تذهب.
Anyway, that house
على أي حال ، هذا المنزل
will be Su Shengnan and Ouyang Yuchuan's wedding room.
ستكون غرفة زفاف Su Shengnan و Ouyang Yuchuan.
No way.
مستحيل.
I'll go then.
سأذهب بعد ذلك.
That's right.
صحيح.
You're indeed my brother's good sister.
أنت بالفعل أخت أخي الطيبة.
Be good. Go ahead.
كن جيد.  تفضل.
Hey, hey, hey, wait a minute.
مهلا ، مهلا ، مهلا ، انتظر لحظة.
Yes, yes, yes.
نعم نعم نعم.
Miss Leng,
ملكة جمال لينغ ،
what's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Even if your Leng family buys this old house,
حتى لو اشترت عائلتك هذا المنزل القديم ،
I won't marry you.
لن أتزوجك.
After all, this woman
بعد كل شيء ، هذه المرأة
is my exclusive love.
هو حبي الحصري.
I'm so pissed off.
انا غاضب جدا.